Family: Coval
Designer: Stefan Peev
Foundry: Context Ltd. (www.contextbg.net)
Category: San-serif
Description: 
Coval is a free-to-use non-commercial font family, which is is still under development. The base range of the cyrillic glyphs (uni0410:uni044F) represents the modern Bulgarian letterform model. The traditional cyrillic letterform model is included as a local feature for Russian language. In version 2.00 there are many changes including the shapes of the glyphs, metrics, bugs fixing. To receive newest updates of the family Coval, please write to us [ contex.bg(at)gmail.com ]. Coval is released under the SIL Open Font License (OFL) (http://scripts.sil.org/OFL).